Olaf Szyncel

Legionów Polskich 34/31 32-300 Olkusz

573357062 szyncelolaf@gmail.com qithub.com/olafszyncel I am a motivated 3rd-year student at the University of Silesia in Katowice in the field of computer science. I have also been learning on my own for over 4 years, in the meantime completing many online courses. My main character trait is the ability to solve problems and commitment to the project. I am hardworking and creative. I am interested in Formula1, tennis, I also like games and new technologies.

Skills

/ Python / Django / Java / GitHub / SQL / bash / HTML / CSS / JavaScript /

Work Experience

Robert Berger I Tak Zdasz / Math Tutor

July 2022 - Present, Remote Work

Szkoła Maturzystów Korepetycje Sp. z o. o. / Math Tutor

August 2021 - March 2022, Remote Work

FHPU Marlibo / Gas Station Attendant

May 2024 – September 2024, Olkusz

May 2023 - September 2023, Olkusz

May 2022 - September 2022, Olkusz

May 2021 – September 2021, Olkusz

June 2020 - August 2020, Olkusz

languages

english / intermediate level

Education

University of Silesia in Katowice

October 2022 - Present

Computer Science

4th High School in Olkusz

September 2018 - April 2021

Graduation from high school with a mathematical and IT profile.

Courses

CS50's Introduction to Computer Science, Harvard University

Spring 2022, remote course

CS50's Introduction to Programming with Python, Harvard University

Fall 2023, remote course

Project

Caloric Calculator

The application allows users to calculate their calories needs and plan their weekly diet using the Ninja API. The frontend was created using HTML, JavaScript, CSS with some components from Bootstrap, while the backend was based on Python and the Django framework. The project includes calculation algorithms, Django ORM implementation for secure user data management.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)